Watch on kissasia.li
[Road to Success]
[Episode 4]
[Will you coach the kids
to play football?]
Good afternoon.
[Not interested]
Regarding my little proposal yesterday,
could you reconsider it?
No.
So cruel.
Every time he appeared, he acted weird
and had unclear intentions.
What kind of person is he?
Ms. Lin.
Do you need something?
W-We just wanted to ask you
if Coach Wang Fa
agreed to be our coach.
[Winfred]
[School Sports Equipment Room Work Plan]
Ask him.
He didn't just refuse, did he?
-Not—
-Ms. Lin.
You are not brushing us off, are you?
You didn't do anything at all, did you?
How could you wrong me like this?
I am working so hard to find you a coach,
and you say I'm brushing you off.
So,
did he refuse?
Not completely.
That means there is still hope.
I will do my best.
Do you need anything else?
Thank you, Ms. Lin.
-Bye-bye.
Goodbye, Ms. Lin.
Bye-bye, Ms. Lin.
My football lending card.
Ms. Lin,
use your charm.
I need to think of a good way
to deal with him.
Come on.
You know what?
I missed this so much
when I was in the UK.
Didn't the team hire a Chinese chef?
Don't mention him.
He's from Wuxi.
He adds sugar to everything.
Only your favorite student
likes sweet food.
As a result, I had to control
his body fat
and strictly forbid him
from eating sweets.
Sorry about that.
By the way,
any clues on your investigation
of Lin Wanxing?
Not yet.
But I have a plan.
W-What are you going to do?
The floor in my place has water seepage.
I can seize the chance to go to her place
and check her computer.
Go to her place?
A man and a woman alone?
Are you into her?
Can you be serious?
Okay. I'm familiar with this.
Let me teach you.
After you go there,
break her computer.
Back up all files while fixing it.
Perfect.
How is it?
Last time you came up
with a bad idea like this,
you broke my sister's stereo
and took it for repair.
Didn't you almost electrocute yourself?
Well...
Shut up.
Let's drop it.
Change the topic and eat the shrimp.
You are my brother-in-law.
Peel it for me.
Why are you so impolite?
Are you sure
she will invite you to her place?
Probably.
Do you mean
I can't stay at home tonight?
Right, Mr. Wang.
This old house has terrible waterproofing,
so we'll have to apply two coats.
To finish it as soon as possible tomorrow,
we have to work
late tonight.
Okay. No problem.
I can stay in a hotel.
Okay.
He has to stay in a hotel tonight.
Thanks for your hard work.
No problem.
Congratulations. Great progress.
Almost done.
I can tell.
What's up?
I wonder if you agree
to coach the football team.
I told you
I'm not interested.
Don't be in a rush to refuse.
Aren't you curious about the pay first?
Name your price.
Sorry.
You can't afford me.
So pretentious.
I'll bear with it.
I'll waive your rent.
I'll waive it as long as you coach them.
I don't need it.
So arrogant.
Do you know how much it costs
to maintain a football team?
Isn't it still about money?
I'm not sure.
But I guess
most of the expenses
go toward the coach's salary.
Don't waste your time on me.
Find someone else.
So stubborn.
Sir.
Please apply more waterproof coating
on this side for me.
Okay.
Then don't blame me.
I'll take your ID card.
Let's see how you check into a hotel.
Go ahead then.
I won't bother you.
We're doing it very carefully.
[Name: Wang Fa]
[Resident Identity Card
of the People's Republic of China]
To be honest,
Mr. Win's flat 2D portrait
is quite pleasing to the eye.
It's definitely photoshopped.
Once he starts to speak,
he gradually becomes repulsive.
I don't believe I can't win you over.
[Winfred Wang] [Search]
[Winfred Wang]
[Notes]
Cold.
Aloof.
Autistic.
And with typical
obsessive-compulsive behaviors.
He's more than just hard to deal with.
Extremely hard.
[Fragment] [Fall]
Mr. Win,
it's time to show you my professionalism.
But...
he's quite an interesting person.
Rational,
disciplined,
visionary,
and with an extraordinary understanding
of football.
[Tendency-Oriented Methodology
for Rectifying Wang Fa's Conduct]
No.
Why am I praising him?
Tendency-Oriented Methodology
for Rectifying Wang Fa's Conduct.
Let's start with the foot-in-the-door
and suspension bridge effects.
[Make a Strategic Plan]
[Strategic Plan]
[Suspension bridge effect]
To deal with an ordinary person,
these two are enough.
[Foot-in-the-door effect]
Given that he's extremely
hard to deal with,
[Door-in-the-face effect]
add the door-in-the-face effect.
[Suspension bridge effect: Build
tense atmosphere to boost adrenaline]
[Foot-in-the-door effect: Break ice
via physical touch & define core needs]
With such a detailed strategic plan,
[Door-in-the-face effect:
Excessive requests, fallback demands]
I don't believe I can't win you over.
[Make a Strategic Plan]
Strategy No. 1,
the foot-in-the-door effect.
Ask for his help appropriately.
It can make him like me more.
Because after helping me,
he'll adjust his feelings toward me
and think I'm someone worth helping.
Why is it crooked?
Let me help you.
It really works.
Leave this kind of thing
to me.
Being tall really has its advantages.
A piece of cake.
Nailed it.
[Make a Strategic Plan]
Strategy No. 2,
the suspension bridge effect.
When a person is in a dangerous situation,
like on a suspension bridge,
if he meets another person,
he'll naturally develop
trust and reliance.
Here it comes.
The scariest part is coming.
It's my turn.
Who is it?
It's me.
Coming.
What's up?
I lost my ID card.
I wanted to ask
where I can get a temporary one
around here.
It's so late.
They should be closed by now.
Are police stations ever closed?
Are you worried you won't be able
to check into a hotel?
I know
there are a few small motels nearby.
Although the environment is a bit poor,
you could make do for one night.
You really can make things up.
Do you think I don't know
small motels require ID cards too?
I just don't know
if you're afraid of mice or cockroaches.
Childish.
There's another way.
If you don't mind,
I actually have a spare room at my place.
It's a deal.
It went so smoothly?
Sorry about this.
I only have
-pink wool slippers.
-What does she mean?
Is this a psychological trick?
Actually, I don't mind if you go barefoot.
I do.
He's even okay with this?
Ms. Lin, what do you usually do at night?
Read books or surf the internet?
Not picky at all.
Both.
[The Philosophy of History]
To be able to read
an original book like this,
you must be a professional.
I used to be.
None of your business.
What about now?
Now, I'm a proud
Sports Equipment Keeper.
Very vigilant.
Oh no, his ID card.
Look, those are my collected blind boxes.
-Aren't they cute?
-What doesn't she want me to see?
Take a seat anywhere.
He's such a big guy.
Your home
is really crowded.
Crowded?
I think it's very scientific.
Scientific?
Everything is on the line of action.
Isn't it scientific?
I have to find a chance
to check her computer.
I let you sit,
and you're still being picky.
How about
you sit on the sofa?
I'll tidy it up for you.
Are you hungry?
How about I order some takeout for you?
How about a burger?
I don't eat takeout.
Do you have any ingredients at home?
Yes.
In the fridge.
Go see for yourself.
How long have these been here?
I'll just have a burger.
Computer.
I need to find a way to distract her.
This tastes really good.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
The Wang Fa's Strategic Plan
officially starts.
You're quite the actor.
I can't reach it.
Why is it crooked?
Fine then,
I'll play along with you.
This heartless guy.
Hello?
The food delivery is here, right?
I...
My stomach hurts a little.
Hey,
you might have to wait a moment.
I'm a bit slow.
Playing new tricks again.
Suddenly got cramps.
This guy is acting too?
Exaggerated.
I'll go get the delivery.
[Foot-in-the-door effect]
The ID is wrong,
and so is the account.
No more cramps?
Rested enough.
You can have the burger.
So boring.
Let's watch a movie.
Okay.
Watching a horror movie
in the middle of the night.
What is she up to now?
So scary.
Aren't you scared?
Then sorry, Wang.
Don't blame me.
Trying to scare me?
Boring.
Ms. Lin, is there something wrong?
Nothing.
Just wanted to ask
what kind of drink you want.
Water is fine.
Thanks.
Playing mind games with me?
You are still too green.
I still have plan B.
Follow me.
This is my grandparents' room.
It's quite spacious, isn't it?
You can make do here for tonight.
Thank you.
Finally, some peace and quiet.
No matter how hard it is,
it won't be hard for me.
I don't believe this.
You short-circuited
the house last time, right?
Again?
Ms. Lin has so much energy.
Coach Wang?
I'm sorry.
The power shorted out.
Old buildings are just like this.
I'm a little afraid of the dark.
If you don't mind,
let's have a drink.
Really full of tricks.
Alright, I'm not playing along anymore.
Ms. Lin, you seem to really like
using psychological tricks.
For example,
the foot-in-the-door effect.
First, you asked me to do
some boring things,
then you made your real request.
What is this one called?
Is it called the suspension bridge effect?
The horror movie is just a setup.
The power outage in the old house
is the main event.
Once we finish our beers
in the dark of the blackout,
we'll become comrades who crossed
the suspension bridge together.
Right?
Coach Wang,
you're really overthinking this.
I hope so.
But let me make it clear first:
I won't be their coach.
All for nothing.
I'm suddenly a bit sleepy.
[Suspension bridge effect]
Playing games with me?
I guess I have to fix
the power outage I caused.
The circuit breaker probably burned out.
Why is he here?
It's too late now.
Let's call a repairman tomorrow.
Wait a minute.
Thanks.
The circuit breaker has been replaced.
The pipes will be fixed today.
Thank you for taking me in, Miss Landlady.
He's even harder
to deal with than I thought.
But...
I have my ways.
[Door-in-the-face effect:
Excessive requests, fallback demands]
Strategy No. 3,
the door-in-the-face effect.
When you want to open the skylight,
you can ask to remove the roof first.
Under extreme shock,
the request for a skylight
will be accepted.
Door-in-the-face effect.
Could it be too extreme?
[Director Qian]
Director Qian is putting pressure
on me again.
Better you than me.
Sorry, Wang Fa.
Time to cross the Rubicon.
I can only bet on this.
I came because I just used
the water upstairs.
Has it affected you?
Everything is normal.
No leaks.
Good.
Wait.
I have a very sincere request.
I told you.
I don't want to be their coach.
Then be my boyfriend.
Is it that scary?
These cookies represent my love for you.
The door-in-the-face effect.
First make a request
that the other person
can't possibly accept,
then lower the difficulty,
and then make a request
that is relatively easy to accept.
You did your research.
So, Ms. Lin, you think
that being your boyfriend
is harder for me to accept
than being their football coach, right?
Isn't it?
Not necessarily.
In terms of shamelessness,
I really lost.
Anything else,
Ms. Lin?
It's your specialty
and you're good at it.
What's wrong with earning
some extra money?
Football is not a game.
It's not as simple as you think.
I don't understand football,
but the kids of the Hongjing team do.
They really need a professional coach.
Because they need it,
others should sacrifice?
You can think about it again.
You just don't know them.
Do you?
I...
Why do they play football?
What formations are they good at?
What are their strengths
and weaknesses?
Do you know everything?
What does football mean to them?
An interest,
a hobby,
or their whole future?
You don't even know any of these,
yet you talk to me about their needs.
When I was a coach in Nanton before,
not to exaggerate,
the youth team I coached
was full of gifted boys.
I'm not suitable
for the Hongjing team,
and I am not interested.
Do you understand them?
Why do they play football?
What formations are they good at?
What are their strengths
and weaknesses?
What does football mean to them?
An interest,
a hobby,
or their whole future?
You don't even know any of these,
yet you talk to me about their needs.
When I took the time to learn about
these kids' pasts,
my heart
couldn't calm down for a long time.
[Report on the Recruitment
of the Football Intensive Training Class]
Report on the Recruitment
of the Football Intensive Training Class.
The Education Committee
of Hongjing No. 8 High School has decided
to establish a football team.
Fu Xinshu, Qi Liang.
Report on the Disbandment
of the Football Intensive Training Class.
[Report on the Disbandment
of the Football Intensive Training Class]
Coach Jiang of the football team resigned.
The Education Committee has decided...
[Spade Q, Lin Wanxing]
[British overseas student,
majoring in Psychology]
[Loves spicy food, hates coriander]
[Bad at sports, can't ride a bike]
Lin Wanxing,
I must know if you are the Spade Q.
You really entered her house?
And then what?
I secretly checked her QQ.
Did you find anything?
Is she the Spade Q?
The name is different.
So what are you going to do?
Look for another chance
to observe her further.
What do you mean by "further"?
Break the water pipes again?
And live in her house?
[Lin Wanxing]
Coach Wang,
a box of books needs moving at school.
Don't hang up.
You'll be paid.
You name the price.
Where are the books?
Follow me.
[Class 12, Grade 10]
Isn't this an empty classroom?
Except for substitute Chen Weidong,
the team members were specially recruited
into Hongjing No. 8 High School.
Here
used to be Class 12, Grade 10,
the Sports Specialty Class.
Since middle school,
they've been teammates
and classmates.
They studied
and trained together.
[Class 12, Grade 10,
Hongjing No. 8 High School]
They were very close.
-Coming!
-Come on.
Feng Suo, come on.
Once more. Once more.
Later,
the coach who promised
to lead the team didn't show up,
and their forward transferred
to another school.
The football team and the specialty class
were disbanded.
They were put into different classes.
[Class 5, Grade 12]
No. 9 Qin Ao
is an aggressive forward
and the main scorer.
He's very explosive.
Although he is usually loud
and looks careless,
he actually has a high offensive awareness
and is good at dribbling past defenders.
The one next to him is Lin Lu,
a center-back.
He is
the smallest in the team,
but very agile.
The curly-haired guy
they're always messing with
is Yu Ming.
He's a left-back.
He's very well-behaved.
He can firmly execute assigned tactics.
He's absolutely reliable.
Ms. Lin?
What is she doing here?
Looking for the coach.
The one doing homework is Fu Xinshu.
He's our captain
and the pillar of the team.
He is the one
most passionate about football.
Hello, Ms. Lin. Hello, Coach.
Go back to your homework.
Okay.
And over there.
This way.
You have 10 minutes left.
How come I only have 10 minutes?
Because my patience
will only last 10 more minutes.
Just get straight to the point.
Alright.
Asking you to move books was a lie.
I just hoped that you
could get to know those boys properly.
I've known them.
So what?
Maybe you'd be willing
to change your mind.
Actually, those kids are quite pitiful.
Except for the students
on the football team,
no one else wants to play with them.
They have been marginalized.
Ms. Lin,
what kind of psychological effect is this?
Emotional blackmail?
Of course not.
Actually,
I have a question
I want to ask you, Coach Wang.
Many of them say
they never want to play football again.
Do you think it's true?
Judging from their performance
on the pitch,
it doesn't seem like it.
Then I was right.
They were once
abandoned by their coach
and their teammates,
and lost the chance to play football.
Because they are heartbroken,
they shout loudly,
"To hell with football,
I will never play again!"
But once they get on the pitch,
they still run so hard
and give it their all.
Even an amateur like me
can tell they're not telling the truth.
Don't easily
fall into the self-satisfaction
of saving others,
Ms. Lin.
Fine.
To be honest,
I came to this school
to be the Sports Equipment Keeper
just for an easier life.
I hope you can come and be the coach
for the same reason.
If you can,
you can ease my burden
and save my job.
In human communication,
sincerity is the ultimate weapon.
I admit
I did use
some psychological effects earlier
to try and persuade you.
This ID card
was also taken by me.
[Name: Wang Fa]
Here you go.
My actions were calculated,
but my desire for you to be the coach
is sincere.
Coach Wang Fa,
I sincerely beg you once again
to become the team's coach.
Help them
and help me.
What do you mean by "further"?
Break the water pipes again?
And move into her house?
I think you're starting to win me over.
Really?
But I have a condition.
What is it?
Let's make a bet.
You experience my disciplined lifestyle.
If you can stick to it,
I might agree.
No...
But since it's a bet,
shouldn't you also join in
and experience my lifestyle?
Whoever can't endure it
loses.
Deal.
[Good morning]
It's the weekend today.
Who is it?
Coach Wang,
do you know what time it is?
Who agreed to swap lives yesterday?
But it's too early.
It's not early.
Usually at this time,
I've already started my morning run.
Bro, are you even human?
How about this? Let's set the rules first.
There are rules?
Why didn't you say so yesterday?
Speechless.
[Time] [Training Schedule]
[Key Objectives] [Remarks]
Fasted cardio.
[Wake Up & Warm-up Activation]
[Fasted Cardio Session]
6 a.m.
[Indoor Cardio Training] [Dinner Time]
[Evening Cardio]
Evening cardio.
Coach,
your schedule
is stricter than military training.
This is how I usually am.
Double-digit step count.
Lazing around all afternoon on weekends.
Can you do that?
I've never seen anyone so lazy.
I can.
Then...
eating river snail rice noodles barefoot,
and doing handstands in a lace slip dress
while eating spicy wheat gluten snacks.
You can do those too?
You're pushing your luck.
Your usual hobbies
are quite unique.
So,
you see, you can't accept them either.
Swapping lives requires
reasonable requests.
The fasted cardio,
[Indoor Cardio Training] [Dinner Time]
[Evening Cardio]
physical training,
and night jogging should all be deleted.
Let's compromise.
In the morning,
you follow my arrangements.
Reasonable,
not strict ones.
And in the afternoon?
In the afternoon,
I'll listen to you.
Deal.
♪ There's nothing to fear ♪
♪ Because you're with me ♪
♪ The light shimmers ♪
♪ Brilliant as stars ♪
♪ Running towards you ♪